Technical University of British Columbia fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Office of the President records, 1986 - 2002; F-177-1; 8.65 m of textual records and other material; Dates of creation: Predominant dates of the series are 1995-2002. Physical description: Includes 46 photographs, 3 contact sheets, 14 videocassettes, 3 audio cassettes, 1 compact disk, and 2 artifa
  - Community relations records, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-5; Analog originals: 12 cm of textual records 2 moving images (2 videocassettes) Digitized materials: Preservation copies - 2 mov files (5.94 GB) Access copies - 2 mp4 files (123.7 MB)
    - Media releases, 1996 - 2001; F-177-1-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 177-21)
    - Opening day, 1999; F-177-1-5-0-9 (Archival box - standard 177-22)
    - Press clippings, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-5-0-10 (Archival box - standard 177-22)
    - Promotional materials, 1996 - 1999; F-177-1-5-0-11 (Archival box - standard 177-22)
    - Recruitment events, 1998; F-177-1-5-0-12 (Archival box - standard 177-22)
    - Special events - university, 1996 - 2001; F-177-1-5-0-13 (Archival box - standard 177-22)
    - Surrey Place Mall, 2000; F-177-1-5-0-14 (Archival box - standard 177-22)
    - TechBC video, 1999; F-177-1-5-0-15 (Archival box - standard 177-22)
      Textual records; Moving images
      - Avatar: TechBC World Prototype, February 17, 1999; F-177-1-5-0-15-1; 1 videocassette 1 .mov file (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2422)
        Moving images; Records in electronic form (digitized)
        .mov file also available in .mkv and .mp4 formats.
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-177-item1.
      - TechBC World Prototype - Avatar, March 9, 1999; F-177-1-5-0-15-2; 1 videocassette 1 .mov file (Videocassette: vhs OBJ-2423)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-177-item2.
  - Financial records, 1997 - 2001; F-177-1-6; 8 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the financial resources of the University. Activities documented include audits, and the preparation of budgets and business plans. Records include financial reports, such as audits and budgets, and business plans
    The material is arranged alphabetically, according to the original filing system of the creator.
    - AGRESSO, 16 February 2000; F-177-1-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 177-22)
    - Alumni/Development System, 2000; F-177-1-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 177-22)
    - Audit, 1999; F-177-1-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 177-22)
    - Budget - general, 1997 - 1998; F-177-1-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 177-22)
    - Budget 2001/02, 15 June 2001; F-177-1-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 177-22)
    - Budget 2000/01, 19 January 2001; F-177-1-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 177-22)
    - Budget 2000/01, 2001; F-177-1-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 177-22)
    - Budget 1999/2000, 1998 - 1999; F-177-1-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 177-22)
    - Budget preparation 1999/2000, F-177-1-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 177-22)
    - Business plan, August 1999; F-177-1-6-0-10 (Archival box - standard 177-22)
    - Finance - general, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-6-0-11 (Archival box - standard 177-23)
  - Fundraising records, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-7; 6 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to fundraising activities for TechBC carried out by the Fraser Valley University Society and the Technical University of British Columbia Foundation. Activities, events and topics documented include the Fraser Valley University Society's involvement in raising funds for the new university, special fundraising events, and the development of the Foundation. Records include minutes and supporting papers; correspondence; reports; financial statements; press releases; transcripts of speeches; lists; invitations; and a constitution.
    Fraser Valley University Society; Technical University of British Columbia. Foundation
    - Fraser Valley University Society, vol. 1, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 177-23)
    - Fraser Valley University Society, vol. 2, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 177-23)
    - Fraser Valley University Society, vol. 3, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 177-23)
    - Fraser Valley University Society event, February 2001, F-177-1-7-0-4 (Archival box - standard 177-23)
    - Fundraising management, 1997 - 1999; F-177-1-7-0-5 (Archival box - standard 177-23)
    - TechBC Foundation, 1997 - 1998; F-177-1-7-0-6 (Archival box - standard 177-23)
  - Human resources records, 1996 - 2001; F-177-1-8; 30 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to staff and faculty positions at the Technical University of British Columbia. Activities, events and topics documented include the recruiting, hiring and training of staff and faculty; terms of employment, job duties and responsibilities; goals and accomplishments of senior faculty members; contracting of Human Resources consultants; performance management; and the activities of the University's Pension Committee. Records include personnel files; job descriptions; contracts and letters of appointment; minutes and supporting papers; correspondence and memoranda; lists; reports and manuals; and notes.
    Technical University of British Columbia. Pension Committee
    - Appointments - faculty and staff, 1998 - 2001; F-177-1-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 177-23)
    - Director, Human Resources, 2000; F-177-1-8-0-2 (Archival box - standard 177-23)
    - Director, Marketing and Communications, 2001; F-177-1-8-0-3 (Archival box - standard 177-23)
    - Employment contracts, vol. 1, 1998 - 2000; F-177-1-8-0-4 (Archival box - standard 177-23)
    - [Employment contracts], vol. 1, 1999; F-177-1-8-0-5 (Archival box - standard 177-23)
    - Executive compensation, vol. 1, 1998 - 2000; F-177-1-8-0-6 (Archival box - standard 177-23)
    - General HR issues, 1998 - 2001; F-177-1-8-0-7 (Archival box - standard 177-24)
    - Glenn Harris (consultant), 1997 - 2001; F-177-1-8-0-8 (Archival box - standard 177-24)
    - HR consultants, 1999 - 2000; F-177-1-8-0-9 (Archival box - standard 177-24)
    - [Faculty interviews], vol. 1, 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-8-0-10 (Archival box - standard 177-24)
    - [Faculty interviews], vol. 2, 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-8-0-11 (Archival box - standard 177-24)
    - [Faculty interviews], vol. 3, 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-8-0-12 (Archival box - standard 177-24)
    - Gordon Walter, 2001; F-177-1-8-0-13 (Archival box - standard 177-24)
    - Pension Committee, vol. 1, 1998 - 2001; F-177-1-8-0-14 (Archival box - standard 177-24)
    - Pension Committee, vol. 2, 1998 - 2001; F-177-1-8-0-15 (Archival box - standard 177-24)
    - Pension Committee, vol. 3, 1998 - 2001; F-177-1-8-0-16 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
    - [University pension plan], 1998; F-177-1-8-0-17 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
    - Performance management, 2001; F-177-1-8-0-18 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
    - Position descriptions, 1997; F-177-1-8-0-19 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
    - Recruitment, vol. 1, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-8-0-20 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
    - Tony Baena, 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-8-0-21 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
    - Victor Barwin, 1997 - 1998; F-177-1-8-0-22 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
    - Deana Brynildsen, 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-8-0-23 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
    - Bill Darling, 1998 - 1999; F-177-1-8-0-24 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
    - Bill De Vries, 1996 - 1998; F-177-1-8-0-25 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
    - Jane Fee, 2000; F-177-1-8-0-26 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
    - Tony Fogarassy, 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-8-0-27 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
    - Tom Gaylord, 1997 - 1998; F-177-1-8-0-28 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
    - Robb Gibbs, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-8-0-29 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
    - Tim Miner, 1997 - 1999; F-177-1-8-0-30 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
    - Graham Rodwell, 1997; F-177-1-8-0-31 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
    - Valerie St. John, 2000; F-177-1-8-0-32 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
    - Wendy Unger, 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-8-0-33 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
    - Sue Wakelin, 2000; F-177-1-8-0-34 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
    - Jennifer Wolfe, 1997 - 1998; F-177-1-8-0-35 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
    - Staff training, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-8-0-36 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
    - United Way, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-8-0-37 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
  - Information services records, 1998 - 1999; F-177-1-9; 1 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of articles relating to the Technical University of British Columbia. Events and topics documented include government support of TechBC, campus construction, particularly with regard to the ICBC partnership, programs of study offered by TechBC, University faculty and staff, and the political atmosphere surrounding the University. Records include copies of newspaper and journal articles.
    The material was arranged according to the original filing system of the creator.
    - Articles, 1998 - 1999; F-177-1-9-0-1 (Archival box - standard 177-25)
  - Legal records, 1995 - 2002; F-177-1-10; 20 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of legal records of TechBC. Includes records documenting legal advice obtained by TechBC for various reasons, including the Canadian Association of University Teachers (CAUT) boycott of TechBC; student-faculty relations; the development of Bill 30; TechBC policy development; agreements with other universities; and intellectual property, trademarks, copyright, and Freedom of Information legislation issues. Includes also records pertaining to financial audits, property leases, and insurance. Records include correspondence; reports and policies; agreements; financial statements; terms of reference; legislation, constitutions and bylaws; and articles.
    - Alexander, Holburn, Beaudin and Lang (AHBL), 1996 - 1999; F-177-1-10-0-1 (Archival box - standard 177-26)
    - Auditor General of BC, vol. 1, 1998 - 2002; F-177-1-10-0-2 (Archival box - standard 177-26)
    - Auditor General of BC, vol. 2, 1998 - 2002; F-177-1-10-0-3 (Archival box - standard 177-26)
    - Copyright, vol. 1, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-10-0-4 (Archival box - standard 177-26)
    - Freedom of Information/Protection of Privacy (FOIPOP), 1998; F-177-1-10-0-5 (Archival box - standard 177-26)
    - In-house legal counsel, 1999; F-177-1-10-0-6 (Archival box - standard 177-26)
    - Insurance, 1996 - 1998; F-177-1-10-0-7 (Archival box - standard 177-26)
    - Intellectual property, 1999; F-177-1-10-0-8 (Archival box - standard 177-26)
    - Kwantlen University College, 1997; F-177-1-10-0-9 (Archival box - standard 177-26)
    - Legal - general, 2001; F-177-1-10-0-10 (Archival box - standard 177-26)
    - Legal - learner/faculty issues, 2001; F-177-1-10-0-11 (Archival box - standard 177-26)
    - Legal firms - general, 1995 - 2000; F-177-1-10-0-12 (Archival box - standard 177-26)
    - Legislation, vol. 1, 1996 - 1999; F-177-1-10-0-13 (Archival box - standard 177-26)
    - Oppel, Wilfred E., barrister and solicitor, 1995 - 1996; F-177-1-10-0-14 (Archival box - standard 177-26)
    - Richards Buell Sutton [legal firm], vol. 1, 1995 - 1999; F-177-1-10-0-15 (Archival box - standard 177-26)
    - Richards Buell Sutton [legal firm], vol. 2, 1995 - 1999; F-177-1-10-0-16 (Archival box - standard 177-26)
    - Richards Buell Sutton [legal firm], vol. 3, 1995 - 1999; F-177-1-10-0-17 (Archival box - standard 177-27)
    - Richards Buell Sutton [legal firm], vol. 4, 1995 - 1999; F-177-1-10-0-18 (Archival box - standard 177-27)
    - Star Trek/Star Fleet, 2002; F-177-1-10-0-19 (Archival box - standard 177-27)
    - Trademarks, 1996 - 1999; F-177-1-10-0-20 (Archival box - standard 177-27)
  - Liaison records, 1993 - 2002; F-177-1-11; 1.87 m of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to TechBC's collaboration and liaison with other universities and colleges; municipal, provincial and federal governments; external organizations, associations, councils, and committees; and the community. Records include correspondence; reports, proposals, papers, and briefing notes; minutes and supporting papers; booklets, promotional and conference material, event notices, and invitations; presentations; newspaper articles, press releases, and newsletters; financial statements and grant applications; contracts; and notes.
    - Liaison - associations and councils records, 1996 - 2002; F-177-1-11-1; 83 cm of textual records
      Sub-sub-series consists of records relating to TechBC's liaison and co-operation activities with various associations, committees and councils, provincially, nationally, and in the United States. Includes records relating to TechBC's involvement with the Advanced Education Council of BC (AECBC), Association of Universities and Colleges of Canada (AUCC), BC Council on Admissions & Transfers (BCCAT), Canadian Association of University Teachers (CAUT), Confederation of University Faculty Associations of BC (CUFA/BC), Ministry Joint Planning Committee, Society for College & University Planning (SCUP), The University President's Council (TUPC), and University Public Sector Employees Association (UPSEA). Records include correspondence; minutes and supporting papers; reports, papers, speeches and presentations; promotional and conference material; newsletters and newspaper articles.
      The material was arranged according to the original filing system of the creator. Files are arranged first alphabetically and then chronologically.
      - Advanced Education Council of BC (AECBC), 1997 - 1998; F-177-1-11-1-1 (Archival box - standard 177-27)
      - Association of Universities and Colleges of Canada (AUCC), 1996 - 2000; F-177-1-11-1-2 (Archival box - standard 177-27)
      - BC Council on Admissions and Transfers (BCCAT), vol. 1, 1997 - 2001; F-177-1-11-1-3 (Archival box - standard 177-27)
      - BC Council on Admissions and Transfers (BCCAT), vol. 2, 1997 - 2001; F-177-1-11-1-4 (Archival box - standard 177-28)
      - BC Council on Admissions and Transfers (BCCAT), vol. 3, 1997 - 2001; F-177-1-11-1-5 (Archival box - standard 177-28)
      - Canadian Association of University Teachers (CAUT), vol. 1, 1997 - 1999; F-177-1-11-1-6 (Archival box - standard 177-28)
      - Canadian Association of University Teachers (CAUT), vol. 2, 1997 - 1999; F-177-1-11-1-7 (Archival box - standard 177-28)
      - Canadian Association of University Teachers (CAUT), vol. 3, 1997 - 1999; F-177-1-11-1-8 (Archival box - standard 177-28)
      - Confederation of University Faculty Associations of BC (CUFA/BC), 1997 - 2002; F-177-1-11-1-9 (Archival box - standard 177-28)
      - Ministry Joint Planning Committee, vol. 1, 1998 - 2001; F-177-1-11-1-10 (Archival box - standard 177-28)
      - Ministry Joint Planning Committee, vol. 2, 1998 - 2001; F-177-1-11-1-11 (Archival box - standard 177-28)
      - Ministry Joint Planning Committee, vol. 3, 1998 - 2001; F-177-1-11-1-12 (Archival box - standard 177-29)
      - Ministry Joint Planning Committee, vol. 4, 1998 - 2001; F-177-1-11-1-13 (Archival box - standard 177-29)
      - Society for College and University Planning, 1998 - 2000; F-177-1-11-1-14 (Archival box - standard 177-29)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC), vol. 1, 1996 - 2001; F-177-1-11-1-15 (Archival box - standard 177-29)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC), vol. 2, 1996 - 2001; F-177-1-11-1-16 (Archival box - standard 177-29)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC), vol. 3, 1996 - 2001; F-177-1-11-1-17 (Archival box - standard 177-29)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC), vol. 4, 1996 - 2001; F-177-1-11-1-18 (Archival box - standard 177-29)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC), vol. 5, 1996 - 2001; F-177-1-11-1-19 (Archival box - standard 177-29)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC) - annual report 1997/1998, F-177-1-11-1-20 (Archival box - standard 177-30)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC) - minutes, vol. 1, 1996 - 1997; F-177-1-11-1-21 (Archival box - standard 177-30)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC) - general, vol. 1, 1998 - 1999; F-177-1-11-1-22 (Archival box - standard 177-30)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC) - general, vol. 2, 1998 - 1999; F-177-1-11-1-23 (Archival box - standard 177-30)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC) - annual report 1998/1999, F-177-1-11-1-24 (Archival box - standard 177-30)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC) - minutes, vol. 1, January 1999 - December 2000; F-177-1-11-1-25 (Archival box - standard 177-30)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC) - minutes, vol. 2, January 1999 - December 2000; F-177-1-11-1-26 (Archival box - standard 177-30)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC) - minutes, vol. 3, January 1999 - December 2000; F-177-1-11-1-27 (Archival box - standard 177-30)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC) - minutes, vol. 4, January 1999 - December 2000; F-177-1-11-1-28 (Archival box - standard 177-31)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC) - minutes, vol. 5, January 1999 - December 2000; F-177-1-11-1-29 (Archival box - standard 177-31)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC) - minutes, vol. 6, January 1999 - December 2000; F-177-1-11-1-30 (Archival box - standard 177-31)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC) - minutes, vol. 7, January 1999 - December 2000; F-177-1-11-1-31 (Archival box - standard 177-31)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC) - graduate follow-up survey, 1999 - 2001; F-177-1-11-1-32 (Archival box - standard 177-31)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC) - annual general meeting 2000, vol. 1, 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-11-1-33 (Archival box - standard 177-31)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC) - annual general meeting 2000, vol. 2, 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-11-1-34 (Archival box - standard 177-31)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC), vol. 1, 1 January 2000 - January 2002; F-177-1-11-1-35 (Archival box - standard 177-31)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC), vol. 2, 1 January 2000 - January 2002; F-177-1-11-1-36 (Archival box - standard 177-32)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC), vol. 3, 1 January 2000 - January 2002; F-177-1-11-1-37 (Archival box - standard 177-32)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC), vol. 4, 1 January 2000 - January 2002; F-177-1-11-1-38 (Archival box - standard 177-32)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC), vol. 1, 2001; F-177-1-11-1-39 (Archival box - standard 177-32)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC), vol. 2, 2001; F-177-1-11-1-40 (Archival box - standard 177-32)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC) - University Presidents' meeting, vol. 1, 7 March 2001 - March 2001; F-177-1-11-1-41 (Archival box - standard 177-32)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC) - University Presidents' meeting, vol. 2, 7 March 2001 - March 2001; F-177-1-11-1-42 (Archival box - standard 177-32)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC) meeting binder, vol. 1, March 2001 - July 2001; F-177-1-11-1-43 (Archival box - standard 177-33)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC) meeting binder, vol. 2, March 2001 - July 2001; F-177-1-11-1-44 (Archival box - standard 177-33)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC) meeting binder, vol. 3, March 2001 - July 2001; F-177-1-11-1-45 (Archival box - standard 177-33)
      - The University Presidents' Council (TUPC) meeting binder, vol. 4, March 2001 - July 2001; F-177-1-11-1-46 (Archival box - standard 177-33)
      - University Public Sector Employers' Association (UPSEA), vol. 1, 1997 - 1998; F-177-1-11-1-47 (Archival box - standard 177-33)
      - University Public Sector Employers' Association (UPSEA), vol. 2, 1997 - 1998; F-177-1-11-1-48 (Archival box - standard 177-33)
      - University Public Sector Employers' Association (UPSEA), vol. 3, 1997 - 1998; F-177-1-11-1-49 (Archival box - standard 177-33)
      - University Public Sector Employers' Association (UPSEA) - [minutes and related records], vol. 1, February 1999 - October 1999; F-177-1-11-1-50 (Archival box - standard 177-33)
      - University Public Sector Employers' Association (UPSEA) - [minutes and related records], vol. 2, February 1999 - October 1999; F-177-1-11-1-51 (Archival box - standard 177-34)
      - University Public Sector Employers' Association (UPSEA) - [minutes and related records], vol. 1, November 2000 - July 2001; F-177-1-11-1-52 (Archival box - standard 177-34)
    - Liaison - BC universities records, 1996 - 2001; F-177-1-11-2; 8 cm of textual records
      Sub-sub-series consists of records relating to TechBC's relations with other universities in British Columbia, including Royal Roads University, the University of Northern B.C., and the University of Victoria. Also included are records pertaining to the proposed Sea to Sky University Project. Records include correspondence; reports and presentations; academic, education and business plans; newspaper articles; promotional material, and invitations.
      - Royal Roads application to AUCC, 1999; F-177-1-11-2-1 (Archival box - standard 177-34)
      - Royal Roads University, 1996 - 2001; F-177-1-11-2-2 (Archival box - standard 177-34)
      - Sea to Sky University Project, 2001; F-177-1-11-2-3 (Archival box - standard 177-34)
      - University of Northern BC, vol. 1, 1996 - 2001; F-177-1-11-2-4 (Archival box - standard 177-34)
      - University of Northern BC, vol. 2, 1996 - 2001; F-177-1-11-2-5 (Archival box - standard 177-34)
      - University of Victoria, 1998 - 2001; F-177-1-11-2-6 (Archival box - standard 177-34)
    - Liaison - external committees and associations records, 1995 - 2001; F-177-1-11-3; 27 cm of textual records
      Sub-sub-series consists of records relating to TechBC's participation in non-University committees and associations of an educational, technological and scientific nature. Includes committees and associations at the local, provincial and national level. Among the committees and associations represented in the records are the Lower Mainland Education CEOs (G-27 and G-28), the Provincial Learning Network (PLNet), Canadian Foundation for Innovation (CFI), and Canadian Network for the Advancement of Research, Industry and Education (CANARIE Inc.). Activities, events and topics documented include TechBC's involvement in collaborative projects, applications for grants and funding, and participation at meetings, conferences and special events. Records include correspondence; reports and papers; minutes; speeches and presentations; grant applications and financial statements; notes; and newsletters and press releases.
      - CA*netII, 1995 - 1997; F-177-1-11-3-1 (Archival box - standard 177-34)
      - Canadian Foundation for Innovation (CFI), vol. 1, 1997 - 2001; F-177-1-11-3-2 (Archival box - standard 177-35)
      - Canadian Foundation for Innovation (CFI), vol. 2, 1997 - 2001; F-177-1-11-3-3 (Archival box - standard 177-35)
      - Canadian Foundation for Innovation (CFI) / British Columbia Knowledge Development Fund (BCKDF) research labs, vol. 1, 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-11-3-4 (Archival box - standard 177-35)
      - Canadian Foundation for Innovation (CFI) / British Columbia Knowledge Development Fund (BCKDF) research labs, vol. 2, 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-11-3-5 (Archival box - standard 177-35)
      - Canadian Foundation for Innovation (CFI) / British Columbia Knowledge Development Fund (BCKDF) research labs, vol. 3, 2000 - 2001; F-177-1-11-3-6 (Archival box - standard 177-35)
      - Canadian Foundation for Innovation (CFI)/CANARIE Inc. steering committee, 1997 - 2000; F-177-1-11-3-7 (Archival box - standard 177-35)